Today I will introduce a small technique for changing the version.
Now I see a set of clothes that we have made.
I want to adjust the shirt.
You can add the modified shirt version in.
You can see the straight line of the version after the modification.
The number of straight lines of the original version is different.
Now the condition of the version replacement is no longer limited by the number of straight lines.
You can replace it directly.
Next, we will start the replacement of the version.
Select the original version.
Right-click to replace.
Select the version after heavy adjustment.
Then select the corresponding points one by one.
Press the return button to replace.
Then replace the original version in the same way.
Here we will save the version that has been added.
The replacement is to adjust the position of the straight line point of the version.
Curve, cut, base line, version name and code information.
Sewing line, internal shape, sticker, fabric, name line, draw and button as the properties of the original version are retained.
Here you can modify it.
Adjust the shape of the clothing.
Here you can modify the design of the front of the clothing.
Adjust the size of the clothing.
Adjust the length of the clothing.
This is our replacement function introduction.
Thank you for watching.